save.com 2016-05-07

# Privacy | redplum.com

Jump to:     Ad Choices     |     Safe Harbor Statement     |     Terms of Use

## VALASSIS PROPERTIES PRIVACY STATEMENT

Last Review/Update: June 30, 2015

This Privacy Statement applies to this website and to related websites, applications, services and mobile applications on or in which this Privacy Statement appears or is linked or referenced (collectively, the " **Valassis Properties** ").  The Valassis Properties are owned and/or operated by Valassis Communications, Inc. (" **Valassis"** ,"we" or "us").  We hope that this Privacy Statement helps clarify how we collect and process your information.

This Privacy Statement describes: 

  * The information we collect on or through the Valassis Properties and how we collect it.
  * How we use and process the information we collect.
  * Your choices regarding the collection and processing of your Personal Information.   

Before submitting information to or through the Valassis Properties, please review this Privacy Statement carefully. (If you have not done so already, please also review our **Terms of Use**.)  When you submit information to or through the Valassis Properties, you hereby consent to the collection and processing of information as set forth in this Privacy Statement and our Terms of Use.

### 1\. Personal Information

Throughout this Privacy Statement, " **Personal Information** " means information associated with or used to identify a specific person.  Our definition of Personal Information does _not_ include information that has been made anonymous or aggregated so that it can no longer be used, whether alone or in combination with other information, to identify a specific person.  For example, Personal Information does not include information that allows us to calculate how many users access the Valassis Properties and the web pages they visit on the Valassis Properties. 

### 2\. Information Collection

We collect information that you provide to us and from your use of the Valassis Properties.  The type of information that we collect and how we process it depends on how you use and access the Valassis Properties. 

**a. Information that You Provide to Valassis:** You may provide us with your Personal Information when create an account to use one of the Valassis Properties, register for a sweepstakes or other promotion, request a free sample, contact us for help or information, sign up for newsletters or otherwise voluntarily supply your Personal Information to us.  We may collect location information from your mobile device that is relevant to the services that you access through your mobile device.

**b. Information that Valassis Collects When You Use the Valassis Properties** : When you use the Valassis Properties, we collect information about how you interact with the Valassis Properties.  We use cookies, web beacons and other Data Collection Technologies (defined in Section 4c below) to collect this information, which may include IP address, domain name, browser type, mobile service provider, mobile device type, operating system type, web pages viewed, access date and time, referring website address and website address of the web page you visit after you leave the Valassis Properties.  Some of the information collected may be Personal Information. 

Some of the emails that we send to you may include a click-through link.  Before you arrive at the linked website, you pass through our servers. We track these 'click-throughs' to help us determine your interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications.

Please see Section 4 below for more information about our use of Data Collection Technologies.

### 3\. Information Processing

**a. How We Use Information**

We use the information that you provide to us to operate the Valassis Properties, including:

  * personalizing the types of information that you receive from Valassis;
  * assessing trends in your use of the Valassis Properties or purchases of products or services;
  * customizing, improving and developing content and functionality that helps us better serve your needs;
  * facilitating communication between Valassis and you;
  * effectuating your opt-out of our direct mail campaigns;
  * providing you with information that we think may interest you, such as company news, products, services, special deals and promotions; 
  * displaying third-party advertisements that may interest you based on your activity on the Valassis Properties; 
  * enforcing our agreements with you;
  * sending you important administrative information regarding the Valassis Properties, such as changes to this Privacy Statement, our Terms of Use or our other policies; and
  * preventing fraud and other prohibited or illegal activities.

We and our business partners also may combine different types of information collected from or about you through various sources, including Personal Information, and use the combined information for the purposes described in this Privacy Statement. 

**b. How We Share and Disclose Information**

Unless you have consented, we will not share or disclose your Personal Information other than as described in this Privacy Statement.  We may share and disclosure information as follows: 

> i.    **Affiliates** : We may share your information with our affiliates and strategic business partners;
> 
> ii.   **Fulfillment of Services:** Valassis may retain third-parties to perform functions on our behalf, such as customer service, web hosting, fulfillment and data analyses companies. These third parties may have access to Personal Information needed to perform their functions but we require that they not use it for any other purpose;
> 
> iii.   **Compliance with Law and Fraud Protection** : We may disclose any information, including Personal Information, as we deem necessary, in our sole discretion and without your prior permission, to comply with a subpoena, regulation, binding order of a data protection agency, legal process, governmental request or other legal or regulatory process.  Valassis reserves the right to disclose your Personal Information if we believe you have or are violating our **Terms of Use** or in order to protect or defend Valassis' rights or property, even without a subpoena, warrant or other court order; and
> 
> iv. **Sale or Merger** : If all or part of Valassis (or any of its assets) is sold, merged or otherwise transferred to another entity, we will continue to process information consistent with this Privacy Statement and, when possible, will provide you with notice before Personal Information is transferred or becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

### 4\.   Policy on Cookies, Interest-Based Advertising and "Do Not Track"

**a. What Are Cookies?   **Cookies are small text files placed in your computer browser directories to store your information about your use of the Valassis Properties and your activities online (collectively, **"Cookies** ").  A Cookie typically contains the name of the domain (internet location) from which the Cookie originated, the "lifetime" of the Cookie (i.e., when it expires), and a a randomly generated unique number or other identifier.  

We use Cookies so that we can improve your online experience – for example, by remembering you when you return to one of the Valassis Properties and tailoring content to your interests. 

**b:   Your Control of Cookies:  **If you wish to reject Cookies or manage the Cookies you accept, you may adjust your browser settings to reject Cookies or alert you when a Cookie is placed on your computer. The Help feature on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new Cookies, how your browser will notify you when you receive a new Cookie or how to disable Cookies.   Although you are not required to accept our Cookies, if you set your browser to reject Cookies, you may not be able to use all of the features and functionality of the Valassis Properties. 

**c. Online Advertising** In addition to Cookies, we the Valassis Properties may also use data collection technologies such as pixel tags, web beacons and clear GIF files (collectively with Cookies, the " **Data Collection Technologies** ") that are used in connection with online advertising. These Data Collection Technologies are provided by ad management partners and other third parties. 

We and our ad management partners also may use Data Collection Technologies to record the actions of users of the Valassis Properties, to measure statistics of our marketing efforts, to deliver advertisements on the Valassis Properties that may be more relevant to individual consumers and to improve the consumer experience on the Valassis Properties.  

We support the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising of the Digital Advertising Alliance (" **Principles** ").  This means that we allow you to exercise choice regarding the collection of information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites for online interest based advertising purposes.  More information about these Principles can be found [here](http://www.aboutads.info/). 

**d. Opting Out of Interest-Based Advertisements:   **If you want to "opt out" of receiving online interest-based advertisements, please follow the instructions at [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices) or  <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>.  An "opt-out" Cookie will be placed on your device indicating that you do not want to receive interest-based advertisements.  If you delete Cookies on your device generally, you will need to opt-out again. 

Please note that opting out of interest-based advertising does not mean you will no longer see advertisements from us or on the Valassis Properties; rather, opting out means that the online ads that you do see will not be based on your particular interests. 

In addition, when you opt-out of receiving interest-based advertisements through the links above, Data Collection Technologies on the Valassis Properties may still collect information about your use of the Valassis Properties, including for analytics, fraud prevention and any other purpose permitted under the [Principles](http://www.aboutads.info/).

**e.** **Data Collection by Third Parties**.  Please note that certain third parties that we do not control may use Data Collection Technologies on the Valassis Properties.  This privacy statement does not apply to those third parties or their Data Collection Technologies. 

### 5\. Security

Valassis is committed to protecting your information. We have implemented security safeguards designed to protect your information from unauthorized access and use. 

We strive to ensure that Valassis' agents, contractors or business partners that have access to information in connection with providing services for the Valassis Properties keep the information confidential and do not use the information for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for Valassis. 

Although we work hard to protect your information, no data transmission over the Internet is completely secure and, consequently, we cannot guarantee the security of your information.  Disclosure of information to Valassis is at your own risk.  We urge you to take every precaution to protect your information when you use the Internet or store information on your computer or mobile device.

### 6\. Children

We do not knowingly collect information from minors. To use the Valassis Properties, you must be the age of legal majority in your place of residence. We do not use an "age gate" or other mechanism to determine the age of users of the Valassis Properties. By using the Valassis Properties, you hereby represent that you are at least the age of legal majority in your place of residence. All information provided to Valassis is treated as if provided by an adult. 

If we learn that a minor has submitted information about himself/herself to us, we delete it as soon as possible. If you believe that we have collected Personal Information from a minor, please contact us at [wecare@valassis.com.](mailto:wecare@valassis.com)

### 7\. **California Consumer Rights Information**

A business subject to California Civil Code section 1798.83 is required to disclose to its California customers, upon request, the identity of any third parties to whom the business has disclosed Personal Information within the previous calendar year, along with the type of Personal Information disclosed, for the third parties' direct marketing purposes.  If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to:  19975 Victor Parkway, Livonia, MI 48152, or by email to: [wecare@valassis.com](mailto:wecare@valassis.com).  Please note that under California law, businesses are only required to respond to a customer request once during any calendar year.

Under California Civil Code Section 1789.3, we are required to provide California residents with the following specific consumer rights information: 

> i.    The Valassis Properties are owned and/or operated by Valassis Communications, Inc., 19975 Victor Parkway, Livonia, MI 48152
> 
> ii.   Unless otherwise expressly stated, the Valassis Properties are provided without charge.
> 
> iii.   To file a complaint regarding any of the Valassis Properties or to receive further information regarding use of the Valassis Properties, please send a letter to the above address or contact us via email at [wecare@valassis.com](mailto:wecare@valassis.com) (with "California Resident Request" as the Subject Line). You also may contact the Complaint Assistance Unit of the Division of Consumer Services of California's Department of Consumer Affairs in writing at 400 R Street, Suite 1080, Sacramento, California 95814 or by telephone at 916.445.1254 or 800.952.5210.

### 8\. General

**a. Links To Other Websites:** Certain of the Valassis Properties may include links to third-party websites or services that Valassis does not own or control.  We are not responsible for the information collection practices of any website or service that we do not own or control.  We encourage you to review and understand the privacy practices of third-party websites or services before providing any information to or through them. 

**b. Changes To Privacy Statement:   **The Effective Date of this Privacy Statement is set forth at the top of this webpage.  We will notify you of any material change by posting notice on this webpage and, when possible, provide you with advance written notice of changes.  We will not make retroactive changes that reduce your privacy rights unless we are legally required to do so.  Your continued use of the Valassis Properties after the Effective Date constitutes your acceptance of the amended Privacy Statement. The amended Privacy Statement supersedes all previous versions. 

**c. Dispute Resolution:   **Please see our **Terms of Use** for important information about dispute resolution.

**d. Information Transmission:** The Valassis Properties are hosted in the United States and other jurisdictions. If you are visiting the Valassis Properties from outside the United States, your information may be transferred to, stored and processed in the United States. The data protection and other laws of the United States may not be as comprehensive as those in your country.  By using the Valassis Properties, you consent to transfer of your information to our facilities as described in this Privacy Statement and our **Terms of Use**

### 9.  Questions?

You may contact us at [wecare@valassis.com](mailto:wecare@valassis.com) to request corrections, amendments or deletions to any Personal Information that you have provided through the Valassis Properties.  Valassis will use reasonable efforts to supply you with requested Personal Information and correct any factual inaccuracy or delete your Personal Information from our marketing databases. To honor your request, we will need the exact information you wish to correct, amend or delete.

If you have questions about this Privacy Statement, please contact us at [wecare@valassis.com](mailto:wecare@valassis.com).

BACK TO TOP

## VALASSIS SAFE HARBOR STATEMENT

Valassis Communications, Inc. and its subsidiaries (hereinafter referred to as the (Company) strives to collect, use and disclose personal information in a manner consistent with the laws of the countries in which we do business, and pride ourselves on upholding the highest ethical standards in our business practices. This Safe Harbor Privacy Policy (the "Policy") sets forth the privacy principles that the Company follows with respect to personal information transferred from the European Union (EU) and Switzerland to the United States.

### 1.   Safe Harbor Compliancy Affirmative Statement for U.S.-E.U and U.S.-Swiss Framework

Valassis Communications, Inc. complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Valassis has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Valassis's certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor>

### 2.   Scope

The U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Commission have agreed on a set of data protection principles and frequently asked questions (the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework) to enable U.S. companies to satisfy the requirement under European Union law that adequate protection be given to personal information transferred from the EU to the United States. The U.S. Department of Commerce and the Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner of Switzerland have agreed on a similar set of data protection principles and frequently asked questions (the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework). Consistent with its commitment to protect personal privacy, the Company adheres to the respective Safe Harbor Principles. The Policy applies to all personal information received by the Company in the United States from the European Union and Switzerland. 

For additional information regarding the Safe Harbor Program, see the U.S. Dept. of Commerce web site at <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor>. 

### 3.   Privacy Principles

The privacy principles in this Policy are based on the Safe Harbor Principles.

### 4.   Notice

Where the Company collects personal information directly from individuals in the EU and Switzerland, it will inform them about the type of personal information collected, the purposes for which it collects and uses the personal information, and the types of non-agent third parties to which the Company discloses or may disclose that information to, and the choices and means, if any, the Company offers individuals for limiting the use and disclosure of their personal information. Notice will be provided in clear and conspicuous language when individuals are first asked to provide personal information to the Company, or as soon as practicable thereafter, and in any event before the Company uses or discloses the information for a purpose other than that for which it was originally collected.

### 5.   Choice

The Company will offer individuals the opportunity to choose (opt-out) whether their personal information is to be disclosed to a non-agent third party or to be used for a purpose other than the purpose for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by the individual.

For sensitive personal information, the Company will give individuals the opportunity to affirmatively and explicitly (opt-in) consent to the disclosure of the information to a non-agent third party or the use of the information for a purpose other than the purpose for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by the individual.

### 6.   Onward Transfer

The Company only transfers Personal Data to a service provider, vendor or other third party acting as a processor of Personal Data for the Company (an "agent") where the agent has provided assurances that said agent provides at least the same level of privacy protection as is required by these privacy principles. Where the Company has knowledge that one of its agents is using or sharing Personal Data in a way that is contrary to these principles, the Company will take reasonable and appropriate steps to prevent or stop such processing. The Company will only transfer Personal Data to a non-agent third party where such transfer is consistent with applicable laws and with the notice provided to the data owners at the time the Personal Data were collected.

### 7.   Security

The Company takes reasonable precautions to protect EU and Swiss Personal Data in its possession to prevent loss, misuse, disclosure, unauthorized access, alteration or destruction.

### 8.   Data Integrity

Personal information collected will only be processed in a way that is compatible and relevant for the purposes for which it is to be used. To the extent necessary for those purposes, the Company will take reasonable steps to ensure the data is accurate, complete, current and reliable for its intended use.

### 9.   Access

Upon request, data subjects will have access to their EU or Swiss Personal Data held by the Company and may correct, amend, or delete their Personal Data if it is inaccurate. However, access to such EU or Swiss Personal Data may be denied, when the burden or expense of providing access would be disproportionate to the risks to the data subject's privacy in the case in question, or where the rights of persons other than the data subjects would be violated. 

### 10.   Enforcement

The Company will internally assess the Policies and their practices to ensure continuous compliance with the Safe Harbor frameworks. Any Company employee found to have violated the privacy principles in this Safe Harbor Statement will be subject to appropriate corrective actions up to and including termination of employment. 

### 11.   Dispute Resolution

Any questions or concerns regarding the use or disclosure of personal information should be directed to the Companies' Privacy Office at the address given below. The Company will investigate and attempt to resolve complaints and disputes regarding use or disclosure of personal information in accordance with the principles contained in this Policy. For complaints that cannot be resolved between the Company and the complainant, the Company has agreed to participate in the dispute resolution procedures of the panel established by the European data protection authorities to resolve disputes pursuant to the Safe Harbor Principles, and to cooperate and comply with the Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner of Switzerland. 

### 12.   How to Contact Us

Please contact us with any questions concerning this Safe Harbor Privacy Policy at:  
Valassis  
Attn: Information Security Officer  
1 Targeting Centre  
Windsor, CT 06095  

### 13.   Changes to this Privacy Statement

This privacy statement may be amended consistent with the requirements of Safe Harbor. When we do update the privacy statement, we will also revise the last updated date at the bottom of this document. Any material changes to this privacy statement will also be posted on the company's website [www.valassis.com.](http://www.valassis.com/)

Last Review/Update: June 30, 2015

### 14.   Safe Harbor Certification

Valassis Communications, Inc. along with its subsidiaries, received certification as to its adherence to the U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework. For more information, please read the Valassis Communications, Inc. Safe Harbor Privacy Policy. Copies of our certifications will be listed under Valassis Communications, Inc. on the Safe Harbor List on the U.S. Department of Commerce Web site.

Most Recent Certification: June 30, 2015

DM_US 47942037-8.039667.0126 

BACK TO TOP

## TERMS OF USE

### **1.     General**

The terms and conditions contained below govern the use of Valassis Properties. If you do not agree to the terms and conditions set forth below, please do not use the properties or any information contained therein. By using the Valassis Properties and/or the information contained therein you agree to the terms set forth below.

### **2.     Content**

All text, graphics, user interfaces, visual interfaces, photographs, trademarks, logos, sounds, music, artwork and computer code (collectively, “Content”), including but not limited to the design, structure, selection, coordination, expression, “look and feel” and arrangement of such Content, contained on the Site is owned, controlled or licensed by or to Valassis Communications, Inc. (“Valassis”), and is protected by trade dress, copyright, patent and trademark laws, and various other intellectual property rights and unfair competition laws. Except as expressly provided in these Terms of Use, no part of the Valassis Properties and no Content may be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, publicly displayed, encoded, translated, transmitted or distributed in any way, including mirroring, to any other computer, server, web site or other medium for publication or distribution or for any commercial enterprise, without Valassis' express prior written consent. Valassis does not represent or endorse the accuracy or reliability of any advice, opinion, statement, or other information displayed or distributed through the Valassis Property. You acknowledge that any reliance upon any such opinion, advice, statement, memorandum, or information shall be at your sole risk. Valassis reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to correct any errors or omissions in any portion of the Valassis Property. Valassis does not and cannot review all materials posted to the Valassis Property by users, and Valassis is not responsible for any such materials posted by users. However, Valassis reserves the right at all times to disclose any information as necessary to satisfy any law, regulation or government request, or to edit, refuse to post or to remove any information or materials, in whole or in part, that in Valassis' sole discretion is objectionable or in violation of these Terms of Use. Notwithstanding, you may print or download one copy of the information on this Valassis Property solely for your personal non-commercial home use, provided you keep intact all copyright, trademark and other proprietary notices, and you may print or download the coupons provided on this Valassis Property. All registered trademarks ®, trademarks ™ and service marks that may be used on the coupons featured on this Valassis Property to identify the products and services of other companies are the property of their respective owners. Valassis makes no claims to these trademarks ®, trademarks ™ and service marks. Valassis reserves the right to add additional trademarks ®, trademarks ™ and service marks that identify products and services displayed on coupons featured on this Website.

### **3.     Your Use of the Site**

You may not use any "deep-link", "page-scrape", "robot", "spider" or other automatic device, program, algorithm or methodology, or any similar or equivalent manual process, to access, acquire, copy or monitor any portion of the Valassis Property or any Content, or in any way reproduce or circumvent the navigational structure or presentation of the Valassis Property or any Content, to obtain or attempt to obtain any materials, documents or information through any means not purposely made available through the Valassis Property. Valassis reserves the right to bar any such activity. You may not attempt to gain unauthorized access to any portion or feature of the Valassis Property, or any other systems or networks connected to the Valassis Property or to any Valassis server, or to any of the services offered on or through the Valassis Property, by hacking, password "mining" or any other illegitimate means. You may not probe, scan or test the vulnerability of the Valassis Property or any network connected to the Valassis Property, nor breach the security or authentication measures on the Valassis Property or any network connected to the Valassis Property. You may not reverse look-up, trace or seek to trace any information on any other user of or visitor to the Valassis Property, or any other customer of Valassis, including any Valassis account not owned by you, to its source or exploit the Valassis Property or any service or information made available or offered by or through the Valassis Property, in any way where the purpose is to reveal any information, including but not limited to personal identification or information, other than your own information, as provided for by the Valassis Property. You agree that you will not take any action that imposes an unreasonable or disproportionately large load on the infrastructure of the Valassis Property or Valassis' systems or networks, or any systems or networks connected to the Valassis Property or to Valassis. You agree not to use any device, software or routine to interfere or attempt to interfere with the proper working of the Valassis Property or any transaction being conducted on the Valassis Property, or with any other person's use of the Valassis Property. You may not forge headers or otherwise manipulate identifiers in order to disguise the origin of any message or transmittal you send to Valassis on or through the Valassis Property or any service offered on or through the Valassis Property. You may not pretend that you are, or that you represent, someone else, or impersonate any other individual or entity. You may not use the Valassis Property or any Content for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these Terms of Use, or to solicit the performance of any illegal activity or other activity which infringes the rights of Valassis or others. You shall not link this Valassis Property to any other site without the expressed written approval of Valassis.

### **4.     Modifications**

Valassis may change these terms and conditions at any time and such changes will be effective immediately upon posting. You should check these terms and conditions periodically because your continued use of the Valassis Property will be deemed acceptance of any modified terms and conditions. If you do not agree to the modified terms and conditions, you should discontinue use of the Valassis Property.

### **5.     Information**

Valassis makes an effort to keep the information on this Valassis Property reliable and accurate, but does not guarantee the reliability or accuracy of any of the information on either this Valassis Property or on sites that are linked to this site. Valassis also does not guarantee that the files or information available for downloading are free of infection from viruses or other harmful components. Valassis shall not be liable for any errors or delays in the content, or for any actions taken in reliance thereon. All coupons, offers and promotions on this site are subject to change without notice. Valassis provides you, our visitors, a venue for obtaining the information contained in this Valassis Property and has no control over the legality of any coupons or other offers made by Valasssis, the ability of any of the other companies to complete the sales in accordance with the offers, or the quality of the goods and/or services offered by the other companies. Valassis has no control over whether the other companies will honor the offers and coupons shown on this Valassis Property and does not guarantee the accuracy or completeness of the information contained on this Valassis Property. In the event you have a dispute with another company in any way relating to this Valassis Property or the use of information from this Valassis Property, you agree to waive and release Valassis from any and all claims, demands, actions, damages (actual and consequential), losses, costs or expenses of every kind and nature, known and unknown, disclosed and undisclosed relating to that dispute.

### **6.     Limitation On Liability**

YOU ASSUME COMPLETE RESPONSIBILITY AND RISK FOR YOUR USE OF THIS WEB SITE. Valassis MAKES NO EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, REPRESENTATIONS OR ENDORSEMENTS (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, WARRANTIES OF TITLE OR NON- INFRINGEMENT OR THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE). Valassis DOES NOT WARRANTY THAT THE WEB SITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE OR THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED. THE WEB SITE IS PROVIDED "AS-IS." Under no circumstances will Valassis be liable for any damages (including, but not limited to, special, incidental, consequential or indirect damages) arising out of the use of, or the inability to use, this Valassis Property, even if Valassis has been advised of the possibility of such damages.

### **7.     Termination of Use**

Valassis may, in its sole discretion, terminate your account or your use of the Valassis Property at anytime. Valassis reserves the right to change, suspend, or discontinue all or any aspects of the Site at any time without prior notice.

### **8.     Miscellaneous**

You may not use the Services and may not accept the Terms if (a) you are not of legal age (at least 18 years old) to form a binding contract with Red Plum, or (b) you are a person barred from receiving the Services under the laws of the United States or other countries including the country in which you are resident or from which you use the Services.

These terms and conditions shall be governed by the laws of the State of Michigan (without regard to the rules governing conflicts or choice of laws), and any action shall be initiated and maintained exclusively in a forum of competent jurisdiction in the State of Michigan. They contain the entire understanding and agreement of the parties relating to the subject matter. In the event that any provision of these terms and conditions is determined to be invalid, unenforceable or otherwise illegal, such provision shall be deemed severed and the remainder of the terms and conditions shall remain in full force and effect. No term or condition shall be deemed waived, and no breach shall be deemed excused, unless such waiver is in writing and is executed by the party against whom such waiver or excuse is claimed.

BACK TO TOP
